<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Ninja-Dojo]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Ninja-Dojo]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/ninja-dojo/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 03:11:30 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/ninja-dojo/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Martial Arts For Adults Classes are fun, exciting, and open to anyone with the desire to learn. Our Dojo is also one of the few places in the world where you can learn the skills of Ninjutsu. These were the once secrets skills of the Japanese Ninja. These skills include not only unarmed combat, but also stealth, weapons and escaping techniques. Our step by step process allows anyone to succeed. Check us out and see for yourself. Get a FREE class here…</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://coloradoninjutsu.com/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3ee38b13-5793-44fb-9784-86a67931efc8</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 05:17:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>One on One Ninjutsu Martial Arts & Sword training… Learn from Colorado’s ONLY Certified Master Ninjutsu Instructor… Contact me to apply.   Download Your FREE Training Certificate with Sensei Benson  Name:  Email:      5 Star REviews  "LOVE this place, excellent instruction, fair prices and great people." - Jen "The absolute BEST dojo in Colorado for Ninjutsu and Jujutsu" - Chris Cord "If you're looking for real ninjutsu and jujutsu, then this is the place you need to be" - JD Goodwin read more... “The absolute BEST dojo in Colorado for Ninjutsu and Jujutsu” —Chris Cord Fantastic martial arts are taught there. Not for everybody, if you can’t behave in kids class they won’t train you. Good for them having standards and sticking with them. Same thing in adult classes if you’re a thug or a jerk they ask you not to train, which is great for those of us that want to train with good fun people. Some people might think they are elitists, but since they are the best school that I have trained at they can afford to be. You can’t find a better school in my opinion. —Jen Fairbanks Both of our kids, a girl & boy, have been with Sensei Benson for nearly 10 years. They’ve moved from the kid’s classes to the adult classes and have enjoyed every minute. We “shopped around” at first, but no one came close to Sensei Benson’s approach and expectation for developing the “whole person.” “Kaizen” – or “continuous improvement” is more than a business name here. If you desire the self-discipline of body and mind that authentic martial arts is about, then you can learn it here. My kids developed excellent skills to the point that I worry much less about my daughter walking across her college campus. But my real thanks to Sensei is for their well-developed sense of constant awareness of their surroundings, personal confidence and the impact of their actions on those around them. I give Kaizen Martial Arts an A+++ —Wendy Adams If you’re looking for real ninjutsu and jujutsu, then this is the place you need to be —JD Goodwin Best dojo ever…sometimes funny, always skilled instruction in a discipline that is still an art and hasn’t been watered down into a “sport”. —Daniel Hocker This Martial Arts Studio is the REAL deal! Forget Karate, Kung Fu or TaeKownDo, I’ll take a real Ninja master any day of the week. GREAT instruction, FAIR prices, FUN environment. —Christopher Lee A Message from Sensei Benson</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ninja-dojo/one-on-one-ninjutsu-martial-arts-and-sword-training-learn-fro/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0d58d17b-1d21-49e6-9a19-1bfce66c44da</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2015 03:09:36 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Contact Us If you have any questions, we would love to help. Get In Touch  Name   Email Address 4 + 12 =    Message  SubmitReset Directions and Phone for Kaizen Martial Arts in Littleton, CO Samurai Museum 5914 S Kipling Pkwy Littleton, CO Location & Hours https://www.google.com/maps/place/Kaizen+Martial+Arts/@39.608855,-105.108163,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m2!3m1!1s0x0:0xa63533bf87bd4b89 Phone: (303) 932-2090 eMail: sensei@coloradoninjutsu.com Be Sociable, Share!</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ninja-dojo/contact-us-if-you-have-any-questions-we-would-love-to-help/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2e12954d-0997-4d04-bc07-033b77a7a1a8</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 18:19:41 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Kids LOVE Our Classes You’ll love what we do for your child in our school. Improved confidence and self esteem is a gift that lasts for a lifetime. Martial arts is absolutely the best way for a child to learn both. Make the time and we guarantee that you won’t be disappointed by our first class facility, dynamic instructors and our top of the line customer service. We all know the rewards of having a child involved in martial arts. Why not give your child those advantages starting today? Bring your child by for a free, no obligation, class and see if martial arts is a good fit. Learn more here…</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ninja-dojo/kids-love-our-classes-youll-love-what-we-do-for-your-child/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ee320ff6-9314-4b36-bea4-7f84852127a6</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 05:22:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>