<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Ninja-Dojo]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Ninja-Dojo]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/ninja-dojo/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 05:22:57 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/ninja-dojo/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Martial Arts For Adults Classes are fun, exciting, and open to anyone with the desire to learn. Our Dojo is also one of the few places in the world where you can learn the skills of Ninjutsu. These were the once secrets skills of the Japanese Ninja. These skills include not only unarmed combat, but also stealth, weapons and escaping techniques. Our step by step process allows anyone to succeed. Check us out and see for yourself. Get a FREE class here…</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://coloradoninjutsu.com/</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3ee38b13-5793-44fb-9784-86a67931efc8</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 05:17:10 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Kids LOVE Our Classes You’ll love what we do for your child in our school. Improved confidence and self esteem is a gift that lasts for a lifetime. Martial arts is absolutely the best way for a child to learn both. Make the time and we guarantee that you won’t be disappointed by our first class facility, dynamic instructors and our top of the line customer service. We all know the rewards of having a child involved in martial arts. Why not give your child those advantages starting today? Bring your child by for a free, no obligation, class and see if martial arts is a good fit. Learn more here…</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/ninja-dojo/kids-love-our-classes-youll-love-what-we-do-for-your-child/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ee320ff6-9314-4b36-bea4-7f84852127a6</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2015 05:22:02 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>